circuitspecialists.com 2008-12-24

# Circuit Specialists Inc. - Privacy Policy / Returns/ Customer Satisfaction

| 

**Circuit Specialists has been in business  for over 30 years!  
**  
**Circuit Specialists Inc.  
220 South Country Club Drive #2  
Mesa, AZ 85210  
**  
Phone: (800) 528-1417 +1-480-464-2485  
Fax: +1-480-464-5824  
Telephone Hours: 8AM - 5PM MST Arizona Time Monday-Friday  

Shipping and handling charges are calculated online. Please call if you have additional questions

For placing orders outside USA, Canada, and Puerto Rico see our [**WEB-TRONICS.COM**](http://web-tronics.com/) web site.

**Privacy Statement:**   
Effective 04/23/2008 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage.

**The Information We Collect:**   
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the _circuitspecialists.com_ and _web-tronics.com_ websites. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

* Name 
* Address 
* Email address 
* Phone number 
* Credit/Debit Card Information 
* (etc.) 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order something online and want it sent directly to another recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

* Name 
* Address 
* Phone Number 
* (etc.)

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.   
We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.   
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.   
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.   
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security :**   
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**   
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Correct Your Information:**   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us:**   
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 1-800-528-1417 or send us an email at [**jr@cir.com**](mailto:webmaster@cir.com) . 

**Note: **From time to time, we get requests to be removed from our mailing list, and continue to receive emails. This usually happens when the email address you are asking to be removed is different from the email address on our list. If you have asked to be removed several times and followed the directions carefully, and still get our promotional email, please send your name and email address to [**jr@cir.com**](mailto:webmaster@cir.com). Please write in the subject box; "still receiving emails, please research my name." We will do everything we can to remove your email address. 

**E-mail Newsletter Usage:** We periodically send E-mail Newsletters to our customers and site visitors with special offers and exciting news about new products. 

**Hassle Free Returns:**   
Any defective or incorrect item may be returned by mail or UPS Ground and must include the proper [**RMA Form**](http://www.circuitspecialists.com/rma.pdf) . Shipping cost will be refunded only if the product was damaged during delivery or if the wrong item was shipped or if the item was Dead On Arrival. Customer damage is not covered by warranty.

**Customer Satisfaction:**   
If for any reason you wish to return your purchase for a refund, you may return it for a refund, less shipping charges, within 30 days from the date of purchase. Item(s) must be returned in re-saleable condition including all manufactures packaging and instructions. To return an item for refund - return it to Circuit Specialists Inc along with the proper [**RMA Form**](http://www.circuitspecialists.com/rma.pdf)

|
